<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>workspacer</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on workspacer</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>changelog</title>
      <link>/changelog/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/changelog/</guid>
      <description>v0.9.11 download installer Workspacer has transitioned to a community project under the workspacer organisation - a big thanks to @rickbutton and @josteink for supporting and facilitating this. We are now actively accepting pull requests.
Features/Additions:
@dalyIsaac (Isaac Daly) Added a beta release branch PR #227 Added gaps plugin PR #193 Allows IWorkspace instances to be renamed PR #190 Fixed ActionMenu location on non-primary monitors PR #184 Fixed the ability to restart with a message PR #191 Fixed wrong workspace for window after restarting PR #183 Handles empty titles for short titles PR #218 Ignores Snip &amp;amp; Sketch PR #189 Ignores Windows 11 start and search PR #221 Layout engines now ignore minimized windows PR #197 Prevents System.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>configuring workspacer</title>
      <link>/config/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/config/</guid>
      <description>Workspacer is configured with the C# programming language. The expressiveness of C# allows you to be hyper-specific in terms of describing your desired behavior. This configuration documentation assumes that you have already created the example config in the correct folder, if you haven&amp;rsquo;t, check the quick-start guide.
I don&amp;rsquo;t know C#, or how to code, should I use workspacer? Workspacer is intended to be on the extreme end of the power user spectrum.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>key bindings</title>
      <link>/keybindings/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/keybindings/</guid>
      <description>the default keybindings are:
keybind description alt-shift-e toggle enabled/disabled alt-shift-c close focused window alt-space next layout engine alt-shift-space previous layout engine alt-n reset layout alt-j focus next window alt-k focus previous window alt-m focus primary window alt-enter swap focus and primary window alt-shift-j swap focus and next window alt-shift-k swap focus and previous window alt-h shrink primary area alt-l expand primary area alt-comma increment number of primary windows alt-period decrement number of primary windows alt-t toggle tiling for focused window alt-p open action menu alt-shift-q quit workspacer alt-q restart workspacer alt-left switch to left workspace alt-right switch to right workspace alt-{1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>quick start</title>
      <link>/quickstart/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/quickstart/</guid>
      <description>Installing Download the installer or the zip file from the Releases page and install/unzip it anywhere you like.
Alternatively, workspacer is available via these package managers:
WinGet
winget install workspacer Chocolatey
choco install workspacer Scoop
scoop bucket add extras scoop install workspacer Workspacer automatically checks for updates. However, if you are using a package manager, you should uncomment/add this line in your workspacer configuration file to disable automatic updates:
context.Branch = Branch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>screenshots</title>
      <link>/screenshots/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/screenshots/</guid>
      <description>below are some examples of common interactions in workspacer, using the default keybindings moving focus you can use alt-j and alt-k to rotate the focused window
moving windows in a workspace you can use alt-shift-j and alt-shift-k to rotate the window order
moving windows between workspaces you can use alt-{1..9} to switch to a workspace, and alt-shift-{1..9} to move a window to a workspace</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
