<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>workspacer</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on workspacer</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>changelog</title>
      <link>/changelog/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/changelog/</guid>
      <description>v0.9.10 download installer  switched to GitHub Actions! (thanks sitiom!) improved font configuration for menu bar (thanks N1x0!) updated to .NET 5 (thanks sitiom!) fixed bug where dangling system tray icon remains after exit (thanks OldKros!) new logo! (thanks BeeryShklar!) improved gap calculations (thanks MSylvia!) added extra configurables for TitleWidget (thanks josteink!) fixed an incorrectly duplicated default keybind (thanks Nicholas Balzer!) added a battery widget (thanks Nicholas Balzer!) documentation updates minor tweaks and improvements  Thanks to: sitiom, josteink, haoxiangliew, BeeryShklar, N1x0, MSylvia, alex-griffiths, OldKros, and wkpalan for the contributions!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>configuring workspacer</title>
      <link>/config/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/config/</guid>
      <description>workspacer is configured with the C# programming language. the expressiveness of C# allows you to be hyper-specifc in terms of describing your desired behavior.
this configuration documentation assumes that you have already created the example config in the correct folder, if you haven&amp;rsquo;t, check the quickstart guide.
a quick note on configuration compatibility because workspacer is a new project, I have not fully nailed down how I want the interfaces to look or behave, so everything in workspacer is subject to change.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>key bindings</title>
      <link>/keybindings/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/keybindings/</guid>
      <description>the default keybindings are:
   keybind description     alt-shift-e toggle enabled/disabled   alt-shift-c close focused window   alt-space next layout engine   alt-shift-space previous layout engine   alt-n reset layout   alt-j focus next window   alt-k focus previous window   alt-m focus primary window   alt-enter swap focus and primary window   alt-shift-j swap focus and next window   alt-shift-k swap focus and previous window   alt-h shrink primary area   alt-l expand primary area   alt-comma increment number of primary windows   alt-period decrement number of primary windows   alt-t toggle tiling for focused window   alt-p open action menu   alt-shift-q quit workspacer   alt-q restart workspacer   alt-left switch to left workspace   alt-right switch to right workspace   alt-{1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>quick start</title>
      <link>/quickstart/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/quickstart/</guid>
      <description>installing download the latest installer or download the latest zip file and extract to a folder somewhere. workspacer automatically checks for updates.
configuring by default, workspacer loads a default configuration, but you will likely want to customize this in order to do things like modify the widgets on the bar, add workspaces, switch workspace containers, or otherwise change the default behavior of workspacer.
a config file can be generated by right clicking the &amp;ldquo;workspacer&amp;rdquo; system tray icon, and selecting the option to create an example config in:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>screenshots</title>
      <link>/screenshots/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/screenshots/</guid>
      <description>below are some examples of common interactions in workspacer, using the default keybindings moving focus you can use alt-j and alt-k to rotate the focused window
moving windows in a workspace you can use alt-shift-j and alt-shift-k to rotate the window order
moving windows between workspaces you can use alt-{1..9} to switch to a workspace, and alt-shift-{1..9} to move a window to a workspace</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
